starnostar.com 2016-03-15

# StarNoStar | StarNoStar Legal | StarNoStar Privacy Policy | StarNoStar Disclaimer

Date: 03-15-2016

## Privacy Policy, Terms & Conditions :

Welcome to Star No Star Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions. Please take a moment and read everything below before emailing us with your comments, questions and concerns.

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy explains how we collect and use your personal information under the [Privacy Act of 1974, 5 U.S.C. § 552a](http://www.justice.gov/opcl/privstat.htm).

By using [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) you consent Star No Star to the collection, and use of your personal information in accordance to this policy. We are committed to protecting personal and private data collected on [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/). We collect anonymous information such as your IP address, browser type you are using, the pages you have visited, and all links and advertisements you have clicked on. We use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a data file that we send "transfer" to your computer and this file is then stored on your computer "hard drive". The cookie identifies your computer to [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) so that you do not have to re-login each time you visit the website.

### Terms & Conditions

Registered and non registered members:

By using [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) you are allowed to browse our website freely and vote as much as you wish. You may register with star no star and keep track of all your votes during your experience on our website. When browsing [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) non personal information "votes" are collected and stored. Please read above under privacy policy which information is collected and stored.

Registered members have the ability to view total votes they have accumulated from date of registration with [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/). Registered members may also delete their profiles at anytime. We give all visitors the ability to vote on any profile in order to give all visitors and members real time tracking of all profiles on our website. We merely collect all votes submitted and in return display the results for any viewer ( non registered or registered member ).

Top 10:

We keep track of the top 10 most popular people on the planet which are voted by every visitor on the website. Visitors have the ability to search any profile they wish to find in our database. If the profile is not listed in our database, users may use the Add New button to submit a new profile.

Submissions:

Visitors or registered members may submit their own profile with all fields completed. Before submitted a new profile to star no star. After submitting a new profile, the profile will go into Pending Status ( not live on star no star ). After careful review from our staff, the new profile submitted will be live ( posted ) on star no star. If the profile submitted is not approved, our staff may or may not send an email responding why it was refused ( not approved ). This applies to registered members only. Non registered members will receive no reply in anyway.

Voting:

Registered and non registered members ( visitors ) may view and vote on any profile they wish. This vote is not limited to just one vote. You may vote on any profile as many times as you wish. After each vote, we randomly select another profile from our database for you to view and vote on. You may alter ( change ) the profiles which are displayed to you automatically by changing the settings.

Non registered members "visitors"

visiting [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) consent on collecting your votes and storing this information into our database in order to give all our visitors real time statistics around the world in real time. No other personal information about you is collected.

Registered members using [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) consent on collecting your votes and storing this information into our database in order to give our visitors real time statistics around the world in real time. Other Member information such as, "username, real name, email, or combination of those, etc" will not be disclosed unless authorized to do so by law.

We collect your personal information in order to:

  * Create and manage your personal membership
  * Provide customer service
  * Perform research for analysis and statistics in order to improve online services
  * Display customized information to your interests and preferences
  * To run contests, and to choice prize winners
  * To communicate with you and provide you new information about our services and changes

### Online Submissions

As of 9/15/2015 there has been a change made for online submissions. Follow us on 2 social sites listed bellow and send us a request/message via one of the following social media accounts you want to be added to StarNoStar site (including names of 2 social sites you have selected to follow).

Visitors "registered and non registered members" may submit new profiles at anytime. When submitting a new profile we review every submission in order to eliminate any fake or inappropriate images, text or any other materials in the submission. Any unlawful information will be submitted to the proper law authorities in order to protect our users and visitors. By using our submission form you knowledge that the information provided is correct to your knowledge. Images uploaded to [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) using our submission form is credited to its rightful owners.

*Registered or non-registered members submitting a new profile agree to the following terms.  
** Uploaded content ( Images and/or Text ) is to your knowledge as accurate as possible.  
** Images uploaded to [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/)

  * must be owned by you. Meaning you own the image uploaded. Or
  * you have permission to repost or reuse this image. Or
  * the image is under a Royalty Free use.

** You are fully responsible for any content ( Images and/or Text ) you upload to [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/)

Visitors and Members uploading images to star no star are the rightful owners of the images and or have permission, courtesy to use these images. Rightful owners of images posted on [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) retain the right to request any or all images to be removed from our servers.

Membership Cancellation:

You may cancel your account membership at anytime. You may cancel by logging into your account and selecting "Delete my account". Your profile will be deleted immediately upon doing so.

### Ownership of content / Fair Use Copyright

Images of people on [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) fall under the Fair Use Copyright. Images of people uploaded to Star no Star are used for visual ( illustrative ) purposes only. Each profile on star no star uses textural information. Along with the textural information, star no star displays an image ( if available ) to depict ( illustrate ) who is being referred to in the text. Images of people on star no star are property of their rightful owners. Star no star claims no intellectual rights to any images of people posted on star no star.

### DMCA Notice

 **Definition of "Private":** Belonging to or for the use of one particular person or group of people only.

 **Definition of "Public":** Of or concerning the people as a whole.

 **Our search results simply reflect what's already out there on the web publicly accessible.**

StarNoStar is an advanced search engine. We are not the primary source of information. We do not own the Internet, and we do not control the content of unrelated sites that appear in our search results. Our search results simply reflect what's already out there on the web publicly accessible.

Procedures for making claims.

### Anonymous requests will be ignored.

### Before doing so, please carefully read:

  *  **Internet Freedom and Nondiscrimination Act of 2006 (H.R.5417, 109th Congress)**
  *  **2008 (H.R.5994, 110th Congress)**
  *  **Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) 17 U.S.C. § 512(f) - Limitations on liability relating to material online**
  *  **Freedom of the press**
  *  **The Universal Declaration of Human Rights**

Freedom of the press in the United States is protected by the First Amendment to the United States Constitution.

 **The Universal Declaration of Human Rights states:**

"Everyone has the right to freedom of opinion and expression; this right includes freedom to hold opinions without interference, and impart information and ideas through any media regardless of frontiers"

Please provide StarNoStar legal group specified information below if you believe your work has been copied in such a way that constitutes copyright infringement. Your DMCA request will be deemed invalid if not submitted properly.

### DMCA Submissions | please provide:

  * Physical or electronic signature of person authorized to act on behalf of the owners copyrighted material or interest.
  * A full description of the copyrighted material you claim has been infringed.
  * Provide a link and description where the infringing is located.
  * Your Address, Telefon Number, and E-mail Address.
  * A proof of identity.
  * You must have a good faith belief that use of the material is not authorized by the copywrite owner, its agent or the law.
  * A full statement, made under penalty of perjury, all the information in your statement is accurate, you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on behalf of the copyright owner.

 **512(f) acknowledgment under 17 U.S.C. § 512(f), you may be liable for any damages, including costs and attorneys' fees, if you knowingly materially misrepresented reported material.**

### Liability

All users, visitors, members are free to use [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) service as is without any warrantee. Star no star makes no guarantees of service availability. By using star no star you agree to all information posted under our Legal Statement. By using star no star you agree to use [www.starnostar.com](http://www.starnostar.com/) at your own risk.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

Star no star reserves the right to change the terms of this policy at any time. If changes are made to our Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions, we may or may not notify you by sending you an email. We encourage you to review this policy whenever you visit. The date posted above is the current policy and terms in affect. Star no star has created a specific email for all your Legal Statements comments, questions and concerns. As well as any abuse of any type you may need to report. Please use [starnostargplus@gmail.com](mailto:starnostargplus@gmail.com) and we will reply as soon as possible.

Thank you,   
From our Star no Star staff
